Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one left to lean on♪
♪لم يبق أحد يمكن الاعتماد عليه♪
♪No way out, no place to run♪
♪لا مخرج، لا مكان للهروب♪
♪Tears held back inside my eyes♪
♪الدموع محصورة في عيني♪
♪I run against the wind and time♪
♪أركض ضد الريح والوقت♪
♪Loved and lost, regrets remain♪
♪ محبوبون وضائعون، والندم يبقى ♪
♪But tears fall down like gentle rain♪
♪ولكن الدموع تسقط مثل المطر اللطيف♪
♪I look up strong, I grow with pride♪
♪أنظر إلى الأعلى بقوة، وأنمو بفخر♪
♪Living life with heart untied♪
♪عيش الحياة بقلب غير مقيد♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪التمسك بقوة♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪الإيمان المتقد الذي أعطيته♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪شفاء الجروح التي نقشها القدر♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪هذا النور داخل روحي المضطربة♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪حياة واحدة للعيش، وهدف نهائي واحد♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪سأحب بشجاعة، بوحشية وحرية♪
♪Break through the noise, let them hear me♪
♪اخترق الضوضاء، دعهم يسمعونني♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪التمسك بقوة♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪الإيمان المتقد الذي أعطيته♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪شفاء الجروح التي نقشها القدر♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪هذا النور داخل روحي المضطربة♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪حياة واحدة للعيش، وهدف نهائي واحد♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪سأحب بشجاعة، بوحشية وحرية♪
♪Break through the noise, let them hear me♪
♪اخترق الضوضاء، دعهم يسمعونني♪
=Dragon King's Decree=
=مرسوم ملك التنين=
=Episode 3=
=الحلقة 3=
If you harm the innocent,
إذا أذيت الأبرياء،
your life is yours to lose.
حياتك ملكك لتخسرها.
Just die already!
فقط مت بالفعل!
If you've dirtied yourself,
إذا كنت قد لوثت نفسك،
then wash away your sins.
ثم اغسل خطاياك.
Why cling to lies
لماذا نتمسك بالكذب
and fall deeper into misery?
وتقع في البؤس أكثر؟
Let nature be free.
دع الطبيعة تكون حرة.
Let all things live as they please.
دع كل الأشياء تعيش كما يحلو لها.
Sink Feng Zhilou into the pond now!
أغرق فينج تشيلو في البركة الآن!
If I survive this,
إذا نجوت من هذا،
I swear I'll rise on my own
أقسم أنني سأنهض بمفردي
and fight alongside the Dragons.
والقتال إلى جانب التنانين.
I'll crush all of you under my feet!
سأسحقكم جميعا تحت قدمي!
Fine.
بخير.
If that day ever comes,
إذا جاء ذلك اليوم،
not only will we kneel and apologize,
لن نكتفي بالركوع والاعتذار،
we'll even
سوف نصل حتى
build you a shrine.
أبني لك ضريحًا.
Remember every word you just said.
تذكر كل كلمة قلتها للتو.
(Feng Manor)
(قصر فنغ)
(Why is the world so big,)
(لماذا العالم كبير جدا)
(yet there's no place for someone like me?)
(ولكن لا يوجد مكان لشخص مثلي؟)
Everyone has a spiritual root.
كل شخص لديه جذر روحي.
Only you don't.
أنت فقط لا تفعل ذلك.
Trash is trash.
القمامة هي القمامة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Mother!
الأم!
(Just because I was born without a spiritual root)
(فقط لأنني ولدت بدون جذر روحي)
(and can't cultivate martial arts,)
(ولا يستطيعون ممارسة الفنون القتالية)
(does that mean anyone can bully me)
(هل هذا يعني أن أي شخص يمكنه أن يتنمر علي)
(and push me to the brink of death?)
(وتدفعني إلى حافة الموت؟)
You deserved it!
لقد استحقيت ذلك!
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪مثل النجوم تتلاشى بسرعة في السماء المفتوحة♪
I never thought
لم افكر ابدا
that in my last moments,
أنه في لحظاتي الأخيرة،
(the only one who offered me hope)
(الشخص الوحيد الذي قدم لي الأمل)
(would be someone I'd only just met.)
(سيكون شخصًا التقيت به للتو.)
♪Like fireflies flicker through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪مثل اليراعات التي تومض عبر العشب البري، ضوء عابر♪
(Why would the heavens give me hope)
(لماذا تمنحني السماء الأمل)
(only to take it away?)
(فقط لأخذه بعيدا؟)
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
(Shang,)
(شانغ)
(thank you for saving me again and again.)
(شكرا لك على إنقاذي مرارا وتكرارا.)
(I'm sorry)
(أنا آسف)
(for dragging you down.)
(لسحبك إلى الأسفل.)
♪Chance meetings fade, just empty rooms left behind♪
♪تتلاشى اللقاءات العرضية، وتبقى الغرف الفارغة فقط♪
(It kills me to leave this world like this.)
(يقتلني أن أترك هذا العالم بهذه الطريقة.)
(I want to live.)
(أريد أن أعيش.)
(Dragon God,)
(إله التنين)
(I'm begging you.)
(أنا أتوسل إليك.)
(Please save me.)
(أرجوك أنقذني.)
♪In that one moment, life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، لم أستطع كسر قبضة الحياة أو التخلص منها♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪
Miss Feng, we owe it to you
آنسة فينج، نحن مدينون لك بذلك
for helping us eliminate this threat.
لمساعدتنا في القضاء على هذا التهديد.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
Feng Manor
قصر فينغ
will count on your marriage to the Lenghou family
سوف تعتمد على زواجك من عائلة لينغهو
to keep us safe.
للحفاظ على سلامتنا.
Zhilou!
جيلو!
(Feng Manor)
(قصر فنغ)
I was too late!
لقد تأخرت كثيراً!
Who gave you the right to use the family punishment?
من أعطاك الحق في استخدام العقوبة العائلية؟
I'm the head of the Feng family.
أنا رئيس عائلة فنغ.
Do my words
افعل كلماتي
mean nothing to you?
لا يعني لك شيئا؟
Father,
أب،
it's not like that.
ليس الأمر كذلك.
Feng Zhilou
فنغ تشيلو
deserved to die.
استحق الموت.
Besides, this decision was made by...
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، فقد تم اتخاذ هذا القرار من قبل...
I have spoiled you too much.
لقد أفسدتك كثيرا.
I thought
اعتقدت
you were just willful.
لقد كنت متعمدا فقط.
I never thought
لم افكر ابدا
you'd plot against your own sister.
كنت تخطط ضد أختك.
Qingfeng,
تشينغفينغ،
you are always too indecisive.
أنت دائمًا متردد جدًا.
We were just
لقد كنا فقط
helping you make the right decision.
نساعدك على اتخاذ القرار الصحيح.
You!
أنت!
You clueless old fools!
أيها الحمقى العجائز عديمي الضمير!
All you ever do is stir things up
كل ما تفعله هو إثارة الأمور
and let Yunqiao do
ودع يونكياو يفعل ذلك
whatever she wants!
كل ما تريد!
(Feng Manor)
(قصر فنغ)
♪Like fireflies flicker through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪مثل اليراعات التي تومض عبر العشب البري، ضوء عابر♪
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts that surge and then unwind♪
♪مثل الأفكار العابرة التي تتدفق ثم تتلاشى♪
♪Chance meetings fade, just empty rooms left behind♪
♪تتلاشى اللقاءات العرضية، وتبقى الغرف الفارغة فقط♪
♪You brought a wave that stirred a wild, restless sea♪
♪لقد جلبت موجة أثارت بحرًا هائجًا لا يهدأ♪
♪Light as a feather, yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪خفيفة كالريشة، لكنها غرقت في جزيرة عميقة في داخلي♪
♪In that one moment, life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، لم أستطع كسر قبضة الحياة أو التخلص منها♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪
♪Like brushing past a butterfly that stirs a sudden storm♪
♪مثل المرور بجانب فراشة تثير عاصفة مفاجئة♪
Impossible.
مستحيل.
♪Like white egrets passing by, turning far horizons into shore♪
♪مثل طيور مالك الحزين البيضاء تمر، وتحول الأفق البعيد إلى شاطئ♪
♪Like someone moving on, lost in their own unraveling♪
♪مثل شخص يمضي قدمًا، ضائعًا في تفككه الخاص♪
Your...
لك...
dragon horns?
قرون التنين؟
♪Leaving behind a smallness carved deep into the heart♪
♪ترك خلفه صغرًا محفورًا عميقًا في القلب♪
You are a Dragon?
هل أنت تنين؟
♪Like one blue brick falling, becoming an ancient shrine♪
♪مثل لبنة زرقاء تسقط، لتصبح ضريحًا قديمًا♪
Did they hurt you?
هل أذوك؟
Mere mortals
البشر العاديون
could never trap me.
لا يمكن أن يوقعني في الفخ أبدًا.
♪Once a mortal heart is stirred, how can it outrun its fate♪
♪بمجرد أن يتأثر قلب الإنسان، كيف يمكنه أن يتغلب على مصيره♪
♪Like a fleeting glimmer you can't return to or reclaim♪
♪مثل وميض عابر لا يمكنك العودة إليه أو استعادته♪
♪Leaving a mark no time can wash away♪
♪ترك أثر لا يمكن للوقت أن يمحوه♪
Dragon God?
إله التنين؟
Zhilou.
جيلو.
Thank goodness you're safe.
الحمد لله أنك بأمان.
Uncle Qingyun,
العم تشينغيون،
sorry for making you worry.
آسف لإزعاجك.
But I'm blessed and lucky.
ولكنني محظوظة ومباركة.
Heaven has always protected me.
لقد كانت السماء تحميني دائمًا.
I should've been here sooner.
كان ينبغي لي أن أكون هنا في وقت سابق.
I should've protected you.
كان ينبغي علي أن أحميك.
Feng Yunqiao,
فنغ يونكياو,
that shrine you mentioned can wait.
يمكن للمزار الذي ذكرته أن ينتظر.
You still owe me a few knocks on the head.
لا زلت مدينًا لي ببعض الضربات على رأسي.
You two survived being drowned.
لقد نجوتما من الغرق.
You must be monsters
يجب أن تكونوا وحوشًا
trying to confuse us!
محاولة لإرباكنا!
Are you fully awake right now?
هل أنت مستيقظ تماما الآن؟
The Dragon himself is here at Feng Manor.
التنين نفسه موجود هنا في قصر فينج.
How dare you slander him?
كيف تجرؤ على التشهير به؟
Feng Zhilou,
فنغ تشيلو
how dare you hit me!
كيف تجرؤ على ضربي!
Why wouldn't I?
لماذا لا افعل ذلك؟
I meant to hit you.
لقد كنت أريد أن أضربك.
Do I need to pick a date for it?
هل أحتاج إلى اختيار تاريخ لذلك؟
You owe me all of this.
أنت مدين لي بكل هذا.
You had an affair with Lenghou Zong,
لقد كانت لك علاقة غرامية مع لينغهو زونغ،
plotted to frame and kill me,
خططوا للإيقاع بي وقتلتي،
and used every filthy trick you could to make Jia Yu destroy my name.
واستخدمت كل الحيل القذرة التي بوسعك استخدامها لتجعل جيا يو يدمر اسمي.
You slandered the Dragons.
لقد شوهت سمعة التنانين.
Your mind
عقلك
is nothing but lust and corruption.
ليس إلا الشهوة والفساد.
As the family's legitimate daughter,
وباعتبارها الابنة الشرعية للعائلة،
you've acted arrogantly,
لقد تصرفت بغطرسة،
seething with jealousy,
يغلي بالغيرة،
constantly scheming,
التخطيط المستمر،
and intolerant of others!
وغير متسامح مع الآخرين!
You!
أنت!
Miss Feng,
الآنسة فينج،
don't provoke the Dragon God.
لا تستفز إله التنين.
Now get down on your knees
الآن انزل على ركبتيك
and apologize!
و أعتذر!
Do it!
افعلها!
Do it now!
افعلها الآن!
Don't let her fool you!
لا تدعها تخدعك!
Dragon?
تنين؟
Feng Zhilou,
فنغ تشيلو
do you think you deserve the Dragon God?
هل تعتقد أنك تستحق إله التنين؟
Demons!
الشياطين!
They're demons!
إنهم شياطين!
Feng Yunqiao,
فنغ يونكياو,
shut your mouth!
اصمت!
You made a mess in front of the Dragons
لقد أحدثت فوضى أمام التنانين
and still refuse to own up to it?
ولا تزال ترفض الاعتراف بذلك؟
You!
أنت!
Are you trying to drag us down
هل تحاول جرنا إلى الأسفل؟
with you?
معك؟
What a shameful sight.
يا له من منظر مخجل!
You old, disrespectful fool,
أيها الأحمق العجوز عديم الاحترام،
your conscience
ضميرك
is no cleaner than hers.
ليست أنظف من بلدها.
Who are you to judge her?
من أنت حتى تحكم عليها؟
Feng Zhilou,
فنغ تشيلو
don't get carried away.
لا تنجرف.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
I'm talking about you, old man!
انا اتكلم عنك يا رجل عجوز!
You're full of talk about family honor and meddling in everyone's affairs,
أنت تتحدث كثيرًا عن شرف العائلة والتدخل في شؤون الجميع،
but all you do is use your power to boss people around.
لكن كل ما تفعله هو استخدام قوتك للسيطرة على الناس.
What's it?
ما هو؟
Just because you're old,
فقط لأنك كبير السن،
no one can challenge you?
لا أحد يستطيع تحديك؟
You!
أنت!
Honestly,
بصدق،
you're the biggest troublemaker in this family!
أنت أكبر مثير للمشاكل في هذه العائلة!
You!
أنت!
And you too.
و انت أيضا.
You abandoned your aging father at home
لقد تركت والدك المسن في المنزل
and treated your wife like nothing.
وعامل زوجتك كأنها لا شيء.
If your mother knew
لو كانت والدتك تعرف
how you turned out,
كيف أصبحت
she'd be rolling in her grave!
إنها ستتقلب في قبرها!
You!
أنت!
Your son is a treasure to you,
ابنك كنز لك
and your daughter is disposable.
وابنتك قابلة للاستغناء عنها.
You worked her to the bone
لقد عملت بها حتى العظم
and forced her to marry an old man as a concubine.
وأجبرها على الزواج من رجل عجوز كزوجة له.
She ended up throwing herself into the river.
لقد انتهى بها الأمر برمي نفسها في النهر.
If I were her,
لو كنت مكانها
I'd come back as a ghost
سأعود كشبح
and drag you down with me!
وسحبك معي إلى الأسفل!
Feng Qingfeng,
فنغ كينغفنغ
surprising, isn't it?
مدهش، أليس كذلك؟
The person you were so eager to see executed
الشخص الذي كنت متشوقًا جدًا لرؤيته يُعدم
is standing here alive.
يقف هنا حيًا.
Are you disappointed?
هل أنت محبط؟
Feng Manor
قصر فينغ
may have given me life,
ربما أعطاني الحياة،
but it never raised me.
ولكنه لم يرفعني أبدًا.
I may be a girl
ربما أكون فتاة
without a spiritual root,
بدون جذر روحي،
but I never deserved death.
ولكنني لم أستحق الموت أبدًا.
You framed me and pinned false charges on me.
لقد خدعتني ووجهت لي اتهامات كاذبة.
You even tried to drown me.
حتى أنك حاولت إغراقي.
I've already repaid the life
لقد سددت بالفعل ثمن الحياة
you gave me.
لقد أعطيتني.
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
we have nothing to do with each other.
ليس لدينا أي علاقة مع بعضنا البعض.
Zhilou,
جيلو،
you've misunderstood.
لقد أساءت الفهم.
you're a daughter of the Feng family.
أنت ابنة عائلة فينج.
You should follow our traditions
يجب عليك اتباع تقاليدنا
and do your duty.
وأدي واجبك.
If you want to leave,
إذا كنت تريد المغادرة،
the only way is through marriage.
الطريقة الوحيدة هي الزواج.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
you can never step out of this place.
لن تتمكن أبدًا من الخروج من هذا المكان.
I'm...
أنا أكون...
the Feng family head.
رئيس عائلة فنغ.
I will stop you
سأوقفك
with my life.
مع حياتي.
What a grand, mighty family head.
يا له من رب عائلة عظيم وقوي.
It's just marriage, isn't it?
إنه مجرد زواج، أليس كذلك؟
Fine, I'll do it.
حسناً، سأفعل ذلك.
But I decide
ولكنني قررت
who I marry.
من سأتزوج؟
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪مثل البتلات المتساقطة، ذهبت مع السحب♪
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪مثل النجوم تتلاشى بسرعة في السماء المفتوحة♪
♪Like snowflakes melting softly in the evening haze♪
♪مثل رقاقات الثلج التي تذوب برفق في ضباب المساء♪
♪Like your fleeting glance that gave me one brief dream's grace♪
♪مثل نظرتك العابرة التي منحتني نعمة حلم قصير♪
♪Like fireflies flicker through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪مثل اليراعات التي تومض عبر العشب البري، ضوء عابر♪
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts that surge and then unwind♪
♪مثل الأفكار العابرة التي تتدفق ثم تتلاشى♪
♪Chance meetings fade, just empty rooms left behind♪
♪تتلاشى اللقاءات العرضية، وتبقى الغرف الفارغة فقط♪
♪You brought a wave that stirred a wild, restless sea♪
♪لقد جلبت موجة أثارت بحرًا هائجًا لا يهدأ♪
♪Light as a feather, yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪خفيفة كالريشة، لكنها غرقت في جزيرة عميقة في داخلي♪
♪In that one moment, life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، لم أستطع كسر قبضة الحياة أو التخلص منها♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪